A Guide to the Papers of the Jefferson National Bank ca. 1914-1998
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the Jefferson National Bank ca. 1914-1998
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
11389
ca. 5,300 items (8 cubic boxes, 15 oversize boxes, ca. 38 linear shelf feet)
The papers of the Jefferson National Bank consists of ca. 5,300 items (8 cubic boxes, 15 oversize boxes, ca. 38 linear shelf feet), ca. 1914-1998, and contains annual reports, statements of condition, histories of the Jefferson National Bank and its mergers, audio and video tapes of television and radio advertisements, posters and lobby cards of advertisements, photographs of branch banks, bank staff and events, printed fliers and brochures about bank services and products, news clippings and scrapbooks, and promotional materials such as hat, cups, and t-shirts.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Stored off-site. Users must request boxes 48 hours in advance of desired use. Neither drop-in nor next-day requests can be fulfilled. For additional information, contact Special Collections.
Acquisition Information
Gift: Jefferson National Bank, March 9, 1998.
Scope and Content Information
The papers of the Jefferson National Bank consists of ca. 5,300 items (8 cubic boxes, 15 oversize boxes, ca. 38 linear shelf feet), ca. 1914-1998, and contains annual reports, statements of condition, histories of the Jefferson National Bank and its mergers, audio and video tapes of television and radio advertisements, posters and lobby cards of advertisements, photographs of branch banks, bank staff and events, printed fliers and brochures about bank services and products, news clippings and scrapbooks, and promotional materials such as hat, cups, and t-shirts.
The history of the Jefferson National Bank, from its inception as the National Bank & Trust Company on September 21, 1914, in Charlottesville, Virginia, to its merger with Wachovia on June 9, 1997, is well documented in this collection. See particularly "Charting An Era of Progress and A Legacy of Service 1914-1997" and the Jefferson National Bank History Notebook in Cubic 3 for a yearly account of various new bank openings and mergers with other banks. The various advertising campaigns of the Jefferson National Bank and the openings of many of the new branches is also heavily documented.
The first series of papers contain the files about the miscellaneous branches of the Jefferson National Bank arranged alphabetically by region. These files contain photographs, sign designs, drawings, blueprints, agreements, correspondence, newspaper advertisements, reports, memoranda, and related material all pertaining to the individual branch featured in the file. At times the files also contain photographs and other material illustrating the surrounding development of an area, such as that of the Fashion Square Mall on Route 29 North, Charlottesville, Virginia.
The second series consists of reports and brochures, including annual reports, 1951-1996, of the National Bank & Trust and Jefferson Bankshares, Inc.; informational brochures about operations, money management, loans and other services, notification of the availability of new services, maps and guides to Charlottesville and Albemarle County, and financial statements; bank charters; history folders, 1987-1993, and a three-ring notebook covering 1914-1997, chiefly concerning the Jefferson National Bank, but also with other files pertaining to some of its predecessors, including the Bank of Powhatan, Bank of Goochland, Bank of Nelson, and Southern Bank & Southern Bankshares, Inc.; news clippings and news releases; logos and related material; statements of condition and quarterly reports; and scrapbooks.
Series three consists of photographs of staff, the construction of new branch offices and other buildings, staff functions, bank officers, the Board of Directors, openings of branch offices and other events, occurring in the Jefferson National Bank, the Southern Bank, the Bank of Goochland, and Bank of Powhatan.
Series four consists of various types of advertising material, grouped by size and type of advertisements, including posters, boards, photographs & illustrations, and material stored in oversize envelopes. Within each group, the advertisements are listed by the slogan or message of the advertisement, except for the advertisements stored in large envelopes. These are arranged according to their "NB" number.
The fifth series contains oversize scrapbooks; the sixth oversize architectural drawings and maps; and the seventh series has audiovisual and miscellaneous materials, chiefly pertaining to advertising but also including some training tapes.
Organization
Series I: Branches of the Jefferson National Bank (Cubics 1-2)
Subseries A: Central Region (Cubic 1)
Subseries B: Eastern Region (Cubic 2)
Subseries C: Northern Region (Cubic 2)
Subseries D: Tidewater Region (Cubic 2)
Series II: Reports & Brochures (Cubics 2-4)
Series III: Photographs (Cubics 5-6)
Subseries A: Jefferson National Bank (Cubic 5-6)
Subseries B: Southern Bank (Cubic 6)
Subseries C: Bank of Goochland & Bank of Powhatan (Cubic 6)
Series IV: Advertising Material (Cubics 7-8; Oversize Boxes 1- 12)
Series V: Oversize Scrapbooks (Oversize Boxes 13-15)
Series VI: Architectural Drawings & Maps (Oversize Tray 16)
Series VII: Audiovisual & Miscellaneous Material
Subseries A: Video Cassette Tape Recordings
Subseries B: Audio Cassette Tape Recordings
Subseries C: Reel-to-Reel Tapes
Subseries D: 16mm Motion Picture
Subseries E: 1" Videotape
Subseries F: Miscellaneous Material including Phonograph Recording, Computer Tape, and Jaz Disk
Contents List
- Branches of the Jefferson National Bank 1963-1993, n.d. (Carton 1-2)
  - Central Region 1963-1993 (Carton 1)
    - A & P Mini-Bank, Barracks Road--Charlottesville 1977-1986 (Carton 1)
    - Chatham Heights--Charlottesville 1989-1990 (Carton 1)
    - Downtown Office--Charlottesville 1977-1985 (Carton 1)
    - Emmet Street Office--Office 1965-1987 (Carton 1)
    - Fashion Square Office--Charlottesville 1973-1985 (Carton 1)
    - Food King Supermarket 1978-1985 (Carton 1)
    - Greene Office--Charlottesville 1985-1993 (Carton 1)
    - Ivy Road Office--Charlottesville 1981-1992 (Carton 1)
    - Kroger Mini-bank--Charlottesville 1985 (Carton 1)
    - Charlottesville Main Office 1963-1968 (Carton 1)
    - McKim Hall Office, University of Virginia--Charlottesville 1991 (Carton 1)
    - Northside Office--Charlottesville 1963-1985 (Carton 1)
    - Pantops Office--Charlottesville 1980-1985 (Carton 1)
    - Ten High Office--Charlottesville 1973-1992 (Carton 1)
    - University of Virginia Office--Charlottesville 1985 (Carton 1)
    - West End Office--Charlottesville 1967-1990 (Carton 1)
    - Westminster Canterbury of the Blue Ridge--Charlottesville 1990 (Carton 1)
    - Downtown Office--Culpeper 1974-1985 (Carton 1)
    - Northside Office--Culpeper 1974-1986 (Carton 1)
    - Fishersville Office 1968-1970 (Carton 1)
    - Fork Union Office 1974-1985 (Carton 1)
    - Chancellor Center--Fredereicksburg 1988-1989 (Carton 1)
    - Fredericksburg Office 1986-1988 (Carton 1)
    - Garrisonville Office 1986-1989 (Carton 1)
    - Germana Office--Locust Grove 1973-1986 (Carton 1)
    - Gordonsville Office--Gordonsville 1970-1985 (Carton 1)
    - Louisa Office--Louisa 1978-1985 (Carton 1)
    - Lovingston Office--Lovingston 1974-1985 (Carton 1)
    - Merivwether-Lewis Office--Ivy 1992-1994 (Carton 1)
    - Madison Office--Madison 1970-1985 (Carton 1)
    - Madison Oak Park--Madison 1985-1992 (Carton 1)
    - Mineral Office--Mineral 1972-1985 (Carton 1)
    - New Hope Office--Augusta 1970 (Carton 1)
    - Orange Office--Orange 1968-1985 (Carton 1)
    - Orange Village Shopping Center--Orange 1985-1993 (Carton 1)
    - Palmyra Office--Palmyra 1985 (Carton 1)
    - Scottsville Office 1970-1985 (Carton 1)
    - Courtland Road--Spotsylvania 1988-1990 (Carton 1)
    - Falmouth Office--Stafford 1986 (Carton 1)
    - Stafford Office 1986 (Carton 1)
    - Staunton Office 1986 (Carton 1)
    - Stuarts Draft Office 1968-1992 (Carton 1)
  - Eastern Region 1985-1993 (Carton 2)
    - Chester Office--Chesterfield County 1985 (Carton 2)
    - County Line--Midlothian, Chesterfield County 1985-1986 (Carton 2)
    - Cumberland Office 1985-1991 (Carton 2)
    - Enon Office 1985 (Carton 2)
    - Manakin Office--Goochland County 1985 (Carton 2)
    - Goochland Office 1985 (Carton 2)
    - Hilltop Office 1993 (Carton 2)
    - Innsbrook Office 1988-1990 (Carton 2)
    - Powhatan Office 1985-1986 (Carton 2)
    - Bellgrade Office--Richmond 1991-1992 (Carton 2)
    - Belt Boulevard Office--Richmond 1985 (Carton 2)
    - Bon Air Office--Richmond 1985 (Carton 2)
    - Carytown Office--Richmond 1985-1991 (Carton 2)
    - Cloverleaf Office--Richmond 1985-1991 (Carton 2)
    - East Main Street Office--Richmond 1985-1992 (Carton 2)
    - Falling Creek--Richmond 1985 (Carton 2)
    - James River Plaza--Richmond 1985-1993 (Carton 2)
    - Laburnam Park Office--Richmond 1989 (Carton 2)
    - Lakeside ATM--Richmond 1985 (Carton 2)
    - Lakewood Manor--Richmond 1985 (Carton 2)
    - Mechanicsville--Richmond 1985 (Carton 2)
    - Parham at 64 West 1985-1991 (Carton 2)
    - Parham Plaza--Richmond 1985-1991 (Carton 2)
    - Second & Grace Streets Office--Richmond 1985-1992 (Carton 2)
    - 7th & Franklin Streets Office--Richmond 1985 (Carton 2)
    - 360 West Office--Richmond 1985-1989 (Carton 2)
    - West Broad Office--Richmond 1985 (Carton 2)
    - Westwood Office--Richmond 1985 (Carton 2)
    - Tuckahoe Office 1985 (Carton 2)
    - Williamsburg Kingsmill Office 1985 (Carton 2)
    - Williamsburg Richmond Road ATM 1985-1993 (Carton 2)
    - Williamsburg South Henry Street 1985 (Carton 2)
    - Williamsburg Shopping Center 1985 (Carton 2)
  - Northern Region 1985-1993, n.d. (Carton 2)
    - Stanley Office--Charlottesville 1987 (Carton 2)
    - Harrisonburg Rt. 33 East Office 1985-1987 (Carton 2)
    - Harrisonburg South Main Office n.d. (Carton 2)
    - Luray East Luray Office 1986-1992 (Carton 2)
    - Purcellville Office 1987 (Carton 2)
    - Stepens City Office 1987-1993 (Carton 2)
    - Warrenton Broadview Avenue Office 1994 (Carton 2)
    - Loudon Mall Office--Winchester 1986 (Carton 2)
    - Winchester Berryville Avenue 1985-1993 (Carton 2)
    - Winchester Boscawen Office n.d. (Carton 2)
    - Winchester Piccadilly Office 1986 (Carton 2)
    - Winchester Valley Avenue Office 1985-1992 (Carton 2)
    - Woodstock Office 1985 (Carton 2)
  - Tidewater Region 1989-1993 (Carton 2)
    - Deep Creek Office--Accomack County 1990 (Carton 2)
    - Great Bridge Office--Chesapeake 1990 (Carton 2)
    - Chesapeake Office 1989-1993 (Carton 2)
    - Churchland Office 1990 (Carton 2)
    - Jefferson Avenue Office 1993 (Carton 2)
    - Crawford Street Office--Portsmouth 1990-1991 (Carton 2)
    - Portsmouth Office 1990 (Carton 2)
    - South Norfolk Office 1990 (Carton 2)
    - Tidewater Operations Center 1990 (Carton 2)
- Reports & Brochures 1914-1997, n.d. (Carton 2-4)
  - Annual Reports--National Bank and Trust Company 1951-1962 (Carton 2)
  - Annual Reports--National Bank and Trust Company 1963-1969 (Carton 2)
  - Annual Reports--National Bank Corporation 1970-1975 (Carton 2)
  - Annual Reports--National Bank Corporation (later: Jefferson Bankshares, Inc.), including the Stockholders meeting 1976-1979 (Carton 2)
  - Annual Report 1980--Jefferson Bankshares, Inc.--Galleys, Draft, etc. 1980 (Carton 2)
  - Annual Reports--Jefferson Bankshares, Inc. 1981-1985 (Carton 2)
  - Annual Reports--Jefferson Bankshares, Inc. 1986-1990 (Carton 2)
  - Annual Reports--Jefferson Bankshares, Inc. 1991-1996 (Carton 2)
  - Annual Reports & Advertisements--Transparencies 1979-1980 (Carton 3)
  - Brochures--Banking Hours 1990, n.d. (Carton 3)
  - Brochures--Branch Openings 1964, n.d. (Carton 3)
  - Brochures--Checking Account 1965-1992 (Carton 3)
  - Brochures--Financial Statements--Jefferson Bankshares, Inc. 1983-1992 (Carton 3)
  - Brochures--Investment Certificates n.d. (Carton 3)
  - Brochures--Loans 1968-1974 (Carton 3)
  - Brochures--Maps and Guides to Charlottesville and Albemarle County provided by Banks 1960-1991, n.d. (Carton 3)
  - Brochures--Miscellaneous 1968-1975 (Carton 3)
  - Brochures--Money Management 1993, n.d. (Carton 3)
  - Brochures--New Services 1964-1992 (Carton 3)
  - Brochures--Printing Specifications for Generic Marketing Kit 1985 (Carton 3)
  - Brochures--Savings Account 1961-1992 (Carton 3)
  - Brochures--Taxes 1964-1985 (Carton 3)
  - Charters for Branches of the National Bank of Charlottesville & National Bank & Trust Company, at Fork Union & Palmyra 1914-1943 (Carton 3)
  - Charting an Era of Progress and a Legacy of Service--Jefferson National Bank 1914-1997 (Carton 3)
  - Corporate Profile--Jefferson National Bank 1993-1994 (Carton 3)
  - Greeting Cards 1995, n.d. (Carton 3)
  - History of Bank of Powhatan, Bank of Goochland, Bank of Nelson, and Southern Bank & Southern Bankshares, Inc. 1914-1985 (Carton 3)
  - Jefferson National Bank History Notebook 1914-1997 (Carton 3)
  - Jefferson National Bank History 1987 1987 (Carton 3)
  - Jefferson National Bank History 1988 1988 (Carton 3)
  - Jefferson National Bank History 1989 1989 (Carton 3)
  - Jefferson National Bank History 1990 1990 (Carton 3)
  - Jefferson National Bank History 1991 1991 (Carton 3)
  - Jefferson National Bank History 1992 1992 (Carton 3)
  - Jefferson National Bank History 1993 1993 (Carton 3)
  - Jefferson National Bank Quality Service Pledge 1996 Jan (Carton 3)
  - Jefferson Today 1993-1995 (Carton 3)
  - Jefferson Today 1996-1997 (Carton 3)
  - Logos, Emblems & Labels for the various banks n.d. (Carton 3)
  - Miscellaneous ca. 1964-1985, n.d. (Carton 3)
  - News Releases--Jefferson National Bank & Southern Bankshares 1975-1986, n.d. (Carton 3)
  - News clippings re Jefferson National Bank, etc. ca. 1949-1993, n.d., 2 folders (Carton 4)
  - Published Statement of Condition--Scrapbook 1975-1980 (Carton 4)
  - Quarterly Report--United Virginia Bankshares 1967 Sep 30 (Carton 4)
  - Quarterly Report--National Bank Corporation 1972-1979 (Carton 4)
  - Quarterly Statements--National Bank Corporation & Jefferson Bankshares (Notebook) 1971-1998 (Carton 4)
  - Reports--Stocks Investment Growth Illustrated, 1940-1964 1964 (Carton 4)
  - Retail Promotions and Plan/Budget 1990-1995 (Carton 4)
  - Scrapbook History of the New Bank of Richmond 1974 (Carton 4)
  - Southern Bank & Trust Company Building Photographs & Related ca. 1947-1957 (Carton 4)
  - Statement of Condition--National Bank and Trust Company & Jefferson National Bank (Notebook) 1946 Sep-1993 (Carton 4)
  - Statement of Condition--National Bank and Trust Company 1967-1985 (Carton 4)
  - Statement of Condition--Southern Bank 1983-1984 (Carton 4)
  - Statement of Condition--Jefferson National Bank 1984-1985 (Carton 4)
  - Statement of Condition--First National Bank of the Valley 1983 Jun (Carton 4)
- Photographs ante 1892-1991, n.d.d (Carton 5-6)
  - Jefferson National Bank ante 1892-1991, n.d. (Carton 5-6)
    - Agribusiness n.d. (Carton 5)
    - Annual Report Photographs 1975-1980 (Carton 5)
    - Board of Directors, Advisory Boards & Officers, including: W. Dale Arbogast, William E. Bell, Jim Berry, George Bull, R. Gerald Cummings, Ralph J. Davis, Channing W. Daniel, Jr., Hunter Faulconer, Henry Harrell, Hiter Harris, Jr., J.A. Kessler, Raymond F. Loving, William E. Maxey, Jr., Leslie W. Minor, A. Preston Moore, James R. Morris, Walter A. Pace, J. William Price, Jr., William Rinehard, and Clay Thompson 1957-1970, n.d., 2 folders (Carton 5)
    - Branch Offices & Construction of Branch Offices (A-H) 1963-1978, n.d. (Carton 5)
    - Branch Offices & Construction of Branch Offices (J-W) 1963-1978, n.d. (Carton 5)
    - Branch Offices & Construction of Branch Offices (Main Office Branch, Downtown Mall, Charlottesville) 1977-1981 (Carton 5)
    - Branch Offices & Staff; including photographs of staff at Winchester, Weems Lane, Winchester, Purcellville, Woodstock, Waynesboro, Harrisonburg, Route 33 & Staunton--(taken out from an album), Williamsburg, Palmyra, Scottsville, Fork Union, Powhatan, and Goochland 1973-1982, n.d., 2 folders (Carton 5)
    - Branch Offices & Staff--identified, including: Thomas M. Boyd, Jr., Lester Carver, Robin Flinn, Don Fulton, Agnes Geer, Clarke Glass, Patty Hanson, Owen Harner, Wilson Harrison, Pat Reed Higgins, David E. Hudgins, Pamela Johnson, Lawrence Kavanaugh, Joseph Kinchloe, Garrett Kirksley, Leroy Lohr, Kay Manchester, Donna Massey, Frank McCue, Groke Mickey, Rosetti H. Miller, Frederic H. Phillips, John T. Rice, Rich Saunders, Clyde Sprouse, Burt Stacy, Susan Stafford, G. McNeir Tilman, Ann Turner, Malion Updike, Bill Watson, Bob White, Stirling L. Williamson, Jr. ca. 1973-1982 (Carton 5)
    - Hovey S. Dabney 1964-1991 (Carton 5)
    - Events--Opening of Branch Offices ca. 1975 (Carton 5)
    - Events--Other Events; Parties, Picnics, Press Conferences, Meetings, Exhibitions, Travel, Award Presentations 1964-1981, n.d. (Carton 5)
    - Events--Retirement Photographs 1965-1975 (Carton 5)
    - Events--Shareholders Roundtable 1977 Jan (Carton 5)
    - Events--Sporting Events 1973-1988 (Carton 5)
    - Events--Unidentified n.d. (Carton 5)
    - New Services n.d. (Carton 6)
    - Past Presidents 1951 (Carton 6)
    - Scott house photograph, at corner of Main & 2nd Street, torn down in 1892, and future site of the National Bank of Charlottesville (see Prints File--Charlottesville--Scott House) [ante 1892] (Carton 6)
    - Slides n.d. (Carton 6)
    - Unidentified Office Sites & Miscellaneous Photographs, including Charlottesville and Crozet 1965-1974, 2 folders (Carton 6)
  - Southern Bank 1937-1978, n.d. (Carton 6)
    - Advertising Photographs 1963, n.d. (Carton 6)
    - Annual Reports 1977-1978 (Carton 6)
    - Board of Directors, Officers, Advisory Boards & Staff Photographs 1965-1976, n.d. (Carton 6)
    - Branch Offices Photographs n.d., 3 folders (Carton 6)
    - Branch Offices Photographs--Main Office, Grace at 2nd Street 1937, n.d. (Carton 6)
    - Events--Meetings, New Services, Visitations, Exhibitions, Award Ceremonies, Parties, Receptions & Sporting Events (photographs of) 1967-1974, n.d. (Carton 6)
  - Bank of Goochland & Bank of Powhatan n.d. (Carton 6)
    - Bank of Goochland--Branches & Staffs Photographs n.d. (Carton 6)
    - Bank of Powhatan--Branches & Staffs Photographs n.d. (Carton 6)
- Advertising Material 1967-1997, n.d. (Carton 7-8 Also OS Boxes 1-12)
  - Advertising--Printed 1996-1997, Advertising Materials in folders (3 folders) (Carton 7)
  - Advertising Boards A-Z n.d., Advertising materials in folders (3 folders) (Carton 7)
  - Advertising--Radio & Television Spots (Typescripts) 1970, Advertising materials in folders (Carton 7)
  - Promotional Give-aways from National Bank & Trust and Jefferson National Bank, including a game "All About Charlottesville" n.d., Advertising materials in folders (Carton 7)
  - The After-Christmas Club Earns 5 1/4% Interest (NB) 1981 Dec 17, Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - Application for Southern Bank's New 24-Hour Teller Card n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - Around Here You're Bound to Feel Close to National Bank (Newcomer's Guide) 1980, Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - Automated Teller--24 Hour MOST n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - The Best Interest Checking is also the Simplest n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - Brochures, Photograph of n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - Budget Checking Brochure 1983 Sep, Advertising boards (2 boards) (Carton 8)
  - Checkbook, Photograph of n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - Combined Statement Brochure--JNB 1984 Oct 15, Advertising boards (3 boards) (Carton 8)
  - Count On Us For The Maximum Interest Rates on Savings Allowed By Law n.d., Advertising boards (2 boards) (Carton 8)
  - Emmet Street Office, Illustration of n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - Fashion Square Entrance Map (NBTC) n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - 5 & 1/4% You Can Count On Us To Increase The Interest On Regular Savings to 5 & 1/4% (NBTC) n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - The Financial Picture For Your Retirement May Not Be Clear--Our Advice On Retirement Plans is (NB) n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - Go Mountaineers!!! We Are Proud To Support You (NB) n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - The Grapevine--News of Note From National Bank (NB) n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - Here's Another New National Bank (Kroger Branch)--NB n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - An Important Notice 1973 Jul 12, Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - Individual Retirement Account--JNB 1985 Dec, Advertising boards (2 boards) (Carton 8)
  - Introducing Jefferson Bankshares, Inc.--Financial Presentation 1980 Feb 21, Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - Investment Savings--JNB 1984 Dec 19, Advertising boards (3 boards) (Carton 8)
  - Jefferson Bankshares, Inc.--Financial Statements 1980 Dec 31, Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - Jefferson National Bank Dividends Visa Card n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - IRA Brochure Insert 1981 Dec, Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - Jefferson Bank of The Valley 1980 Jan 10, Advertising boards (2 boards) (Carton 8)
  - Kroger Mini-bank, Illustration of n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - Louisa Office, Illustration of (NBTC) n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - Madison Office, Illustration of (NBTC) n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - Mail Labels--Northern Region (JNB) n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - Maps and Guides Provided By Banks n.d., Advertising boards (17 boards) (Carton 8)
  - Member NB Corporation Logo n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - Mineral Office, Illustration of n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - More Than A New Name--JNB 1984 Sep 24, Advertising boards (2 boards) (Carton 8)
  - National Bankers Keep Customers' Hours (NBTC) n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - National Bank--Banking Hours 1979 Oct 1, Advertising boards (3 boards) (Carton 8)
  - National Bank Logo 1967-1979, Advertising boards (10 boards) (Carton 8)
  - NB Mortgage Corporation & NB Service Corporation n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - New Hope Office, Illustration of (NBTC) n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - New Hours at National Bank's Emmet Street Office (NBTC) n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - News Releases--Jefferson Bankshares & NBTC 1979 Dec 7, Advertising boards (2 boards) (Carton 8)
  - Now! Banking Hours To Fit Your Life (NBTC) n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - Now! Longer Hours At These Offices 1974 Sep 17, Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - Now You Can Count On Us For The Latest Weekly Rate On 6-Month Certificates n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - $100. Now You Can Count On Us To Offer 7 1/4% Certificates For As Little As $100 n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - Orange Office, Illustration of n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - Our Customers Had A Driving Need For Our New Branch Office (NBTC) n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - Personal Checking (JNB) 1984 Dec, Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - Please Help Us With This Check-Up--Jefferson Bankshares, Inc. n.d., Advertising boards (2 boards) (Carton 8)
  - Put A Little Freedom In Your Pocket (JNB) n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - Private Banking ATM Card n.d., Advertising boards (2 boards) (Carton 8)
  - Putting You First--We Promise! (JNB) n.d., Advertising boards (2 boards) (Carton 8)
  - Puzzled By 24-Hour Banking? The Answer is MOST (NB) n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - Scottsville Office, Illustration of (NBTC) n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - Standard Jefferson Lettering--Jefferson Bankshares n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)
  - Special Jefferson Elements--Jefferson Bank n.d., Advertising boards (Carton 8)